Guide to the New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Committee on Arbitration, 1820s-1973
  - Subseries V.1: Arbitration Cases, 1820s-1973
    - 1914
      - Philipp Bauer Co. v. Proctor Ellison Co. (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Union Novelty Braid Works and Aaron Grabelsky v. Boris Grabelsky (Folder 2)
      - Union Novelty Braid Works and Aaron Grabelsky v. Boris Grabelsky, (2 Folders) (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
      - Wolf, George H. and Edward K. Kern v. Sol Friedman and Co. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - 1915
      - Champlain Silk Mills v. The Williamsburg Power Company (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Eastern Tanners Egg Yolk Company v. F.E. Atteux and Co. (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Eastern Tanners Egg Yolk Company v. F.E. Atteux and Co., (2 Folders) (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
      - Halifax Paper Corp. v. D.S. Walton and Co. (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Pattison and Company v. Joseph Anderson and Company (Box 185, Folder 1)
      - Salvatori and Terrami v. William R. Grace and Co. (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Schiff, Jacob H. v. William Baumgarten and Co. (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Scopes and Feustmann v. Julius C. Bernheim (Box 185, Folder 2)
      - Suffern and Suffern v. Compagnie Marseillaise de Madagascar (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - 1916
      - A.G. Hyde and Sons v. William Iselin and Co. (Box 163, Folder 3)
      - Bradford Dyeing Association v. J. Sachs and Co. (Box 163, Folder 4)
      - Edward Corning Co. v. The Trustees of Sailors’ Snug Harbor (Box 163, Folder 5)
      - Fried, Mendelson and Co. v. Adolph Deutsch (Box 163, Folder 6)
      - Perkins-Goodwin Co. v. The Near Eastern Corp. (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - 1917
      - American Molasses Co., New York City v. W.J. and J.G. Van Dusseldorp, Holland (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Andrew J. Robinson Company v. Trustees of the Sailors' Snug Harbor (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Annin and Co. v. Eddystone Manufacturing Co. (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Doull Miller Co. v. Gontard and Co. (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Esterson and Esterson v. Ostrander and Co., Inc. (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Giannakitsas, Johannis v. Brainard Commission Company (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - H. Mann and Company v. Eagle Hosiery and Glove Company v. I.X.L. Hosiery Company (Box 185, Folder 3)
      - Pattison and Company, Ltd. v. Berg Brothers (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Pattison and Company, Ltd. v. Berg Brothers (Box 185, Folder 4)
      - Procter and Gamble Co. v. E.I. Dupont Denemours and Company (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Simon, G. v. Mart Waterman Co. (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Standard Transportation Co. v. Atlantic Mutual Insurance Co. (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Weinstein, Samuel v. Atlantic Cabinet Company (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - William C. Atwater and Co., Inc. v. The Smokeless Fuel Company (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 1918
      - Albert Heymann and Co. v. Hatters Fur Exchange, Inc. (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Coleman and Company v. Steinfeld Brothers (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Goldsmith and Co., Inc. v. Georges Aubert (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Hudson, Joseph v. T. Richard Denzer and Joseph Nathan (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Masuda Trading Co., Ltd. v. Charles Seligman (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Wood and Selick, Inc. v. C. Caitucoli and Co., Inc. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - 1919
      - Constantinis, Minos v. Minot, Hooper and Company (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Fried, Mendelson and Company v. Harding, Tilton and Company (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - J.H. Rossbach and Bros., Inc. v. The American Metal Transport Company, Inc. (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Marcus H. Harris and Lewis, Inc. v. Banden Colton Company (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Mexico Hide Company v. Lee and Company (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - The Old Strand Chemical and Trading Company, Ltd. v. Magnus, Mabee and Reynard (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Schwarz, Max v. Warren Manufacturing Company (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Utica Gas and Electric Company v. U.S. Structural Company (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Walworth Bros., Inc. v. W. Filene’s Sons Company (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - W.F. Burns Export Corp. v. Edward Le Bas and Company, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - W. and S. Embroidery Company v. Ohta and Rubio (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - 1920 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Citizens Transportation Committee v. Enterprise Forwarding System, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Frank Pinera Company, Inc. v. Janovici and Company, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Innis, Speiden and Company, Inc. v. Ralph L. Fuller and Company, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - New York Paper Handlers Union v. Publishers Association of New York City (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Nielson Company v. Lamah Realty Corporation, (3 Folders) (Box 185, Folder 5-7)
      - Robin, Jones and Whitman, Ltd. v. The United States and Brazil Steamship Line (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Rogers-Pyatt Shellac Company v. E.D. Sassoon and Company (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - S. Caplan and Company v. Alkan, Franz and Company (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Wood and Selick v. The Asiatic Commercial Company (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - 1921
      - A. Rigg and Co. v. Louis Roessel and Co. (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Berkowitz, Herman v. Arbib and Houlberg, Inc. (Box 184, Folder 1)
      - Celluloid Company v. Eastment and Kilbourn (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Commercial Union of America v. F. Souvignier (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Continental Can Company, Inc. v. Vulcan Detinning Co. (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - E. Heller and Brother, Inc. v. S. Malsman (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Essenfeld and Lerner v. G. Colinet, 1921 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Hansen Produce Co. Inc. of New York City v. Republic of France (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Lai Ting Laing v. Caravel Company, Inc. (Box 184, Folder 2)
      - L. Buchman Co., Inc. v. F.A. Cundill and Co. (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - London and Brazilian Bank, Ltd. v. Seaboard National Bank of the City of New York (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Lorraine Manufacturing Co. v. Fried, Mendelson and Co. (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Remonda, Monserrat and Co. v. G.R. Crossley (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Seaboard National Bank v. Royal Bank of Canada (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Siff Brothers Co. v. Robert Baer Hat Company (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - 1922
      - Buchanan, Jones and Company, Edward Nash and Louis Watjen, Ltd., Nash, Watjen and Bangs, Ltd. v. Carleton and Moffat (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Essenfeld and Lerner v. G. Colinet (Box 163, Folder 1)
      - Fairfax Textile Mills, Inc. v. Samuel Sternberger Co., Inc. (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Francis A. Cundill and Company v. Schnabel, Gaumer and Company (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Jones Brothers, Ltd. v. Bardwil Brothers (Box 163, Folder 2)
      - Karp Brothers, Inc. v. S.W. Bridges and Co., Inc. (Box 214, Folder 4)
      - Kaufmann Brothers v. Chartered Export and Import Corp. (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Kaufmann Brothers v. Wah Chang Trading Corp. (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Levy, Robert and Herman Sviridow (Mascotte Dress Company) v. Anna Spencer, Inc. (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - M. Wulfsohn and Company v. Morris Amdur and Son (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - N. Sumergrade and Son v. S. Caplan and Co. (Box 214, Folder 5)
      - National Surety Company v. Henry Kelly Brent (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Shawmut Corporation of Boston v. Habicht and Co. of New York (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - 1923
      - Brooklyn Finishing Company v. Malmut Brothers and Frank (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Cullom, Neil P. v. Arthur B. Raymond (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Flannery, L.V. v. Charles Schultze (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Garza Hermanos y Cia v. Lees Manufacturing Co. (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Golding, Barnett C. v. Safety Steamship Company (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Greek Government v. Bethlehem Steel Co. (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - G.W.S. Patterson and Company v. Brinkmann and Company (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Hadjigrigorakis, M.G. v. Mutual Life Insurance Company (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Hosiery Manufacturers Corporation v. West Branch Knitting Co. (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - James C. Lawton and Co. v. Burns, Elson Corporation (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Kimball, Virginia v. Herman Asendorf (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Morden Manufacturing Co. v. S. Hecht (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. v. Frederick Putnam Platt and Charles Carsten Platt (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Stephens Fuel Company v. Hugh Gordan Miller (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - 1924
      - Boyd, Thomas v. Columbia Smelting and Refining Works (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - B. Axel Company v. G. Colinet (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Busk and Daniels v. E. Lissberger Company (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Crompton-Richmond Company v. La Blanche Kiddy Clothes Company (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - David L. Moss and Company, Inc. v. Jacob Benjamin (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Dias, L. Silva v. Barnet Leather Co. (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Furness Withy and Co. Ltd. v. Emerson-Brantingham Implement Co. (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Gary, Theo H. v. Mrs. Jennie Cohen (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Geo Wills and Sons, Ltd. v. I. Weingarten and Company, Inc./Geo Wills and Sons, Ltd. v. Mikado Importing Company (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Hesslein and Company, Inc. (as agents for Williamson Mills) v. A.E. Rothstein and Company, Inc., (2 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 6-7)
      - I.S. Sherman and Co. v. American Range and Foundry Co. (Box 184, Folder 3)
      - John Barran and Sons, Ltd. v. Burdine and Sons (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Kenilworth Manufacturing Company, Inc. v. Peerless Cloth Exeming, Shrinking and Refinishing Works, Inc., (2 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
      - N. Sumergrade and Sons v. Frank A. Hall and Sons, (2 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
      - Palmer and Pierce v. Bush Terminal Company (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Rosenberg and Adler v. G. Colinet, Newchang through Phil Segalier, as agent (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Sota and Aznar v. The Cranberry Furnace Company (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Vanderhoef, Mrs. Fannie L. v. Deutscher Verein (The German Club) (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Wagner, Abraham v. Rene Arbib Company (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Wah Chang Trading Corporation v. A. Klipstein Company (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Wah Chang Trading Corporation v. Metal Alloys, Inc., (2 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
      - William N. Matsner and Company v. Mendel Lazow (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Wonham, Bates and Goode Trading Corporation on behalf of Shewan, Tomes and Company v. Far East Importing Company, Inc. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - 1925
      - American Trading Company v. Crawford, Hammond and Company, (2 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
      - American Trading Company v. Crawford, Hammond and Company (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Benjamin, Jacob v. William N. Matsner and Co. (Box 184, Folder 4)
      - Colinet, G. v. Joseph Buchsbaum (Box 185, Folder 8)
      - Colinet, G. v. Joseph Schild, Inc. (Box 184, Folder 5)
      - Colinet, G. v. Pottasch Bros., Inc and Sol Eichner (Box 184, Folder 6)
      - Congregation Beth Israel v. Friestadt Underpinning Company (Box 185, Folder 9)
      - Congregation Beth Israel v. Friestadt Underpinning Company (Box 186, Folder 1)
      - David Kramer Inc. v. United States Plywood Company Inc. (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Edward Heymanson, Inc. v. China Hide and Produce Company Inc. (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - F.W. Frost and Company, Inc. v. Knickerbocker Feather Company (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Greenstein, William v. William N. Matsner and Company (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Harry Levy Fur Co., Inc. v. Rene Arbib Co. (Box 184, Folder 7)
      - Horwitz and Arbib, Inc. v. Schaffer Bros. and Samuels and Benjamin Miller (Box 184, Folder 8)
      - Iwai and Company v. M. Gottesman and Company Inc. (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Landes, Herman v. J.C. Siegelman (Box 186, Folder 2)
      - Max Schwarz Textile Corp. v. Manchester Textile Print Works, Inc. (Box 184, Folder 9)
      - Novo Trading Corp. v. S. Rosenfelder and Son, Inc. (Box 184, Folder 10)
      - Oneita Knitting Mills v. Robert Reis and Company (Box 371, Folder 3)
      - Oneita Knitting Mills v. Robert Reis and Company (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Oneita Knitting Mills v. Robert Reis and Company, (4 Folders) (Box 39, Folder 2-5)
      - Oneita Knitting Mills v. Robert Reis and Company, (3 Folders) (Box 186, Folder 3-5)
      - Rosenberg, Abraham v. Meyer Vessell (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Schecter and Bro. v. Rene Arbib Co. (Box 184, Folder 11)
      - Tappenbeck, William v. Wah Chang Trading Corporation (Box 186, Folder 6)
      - Theodossiades, George D. v. M.B. Atheneos (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - 1926
      - Cadwallader Gibson Company v. International Hardwood Company, Inc. (Box 186, Folder 7)
      - Caldbeck, MacGregor Exports, Inc. v. Wah Chang Trading Corp. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Colinet, G. v. Joseph Buchsbaum (Box 186, Folder 8)
      - Consolidated Fur Corp. v. M.S. and K.A. Workman, Inc. (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Crockett, David B. v. Wm. Baumgarten and Company, Inc. (Box 187, Folder 1)
      - Crompton-Richmond Company Inc. v. Princess Shirtwaist Mfg. Company, (2 Folders) (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
      - The Duomares Corporation v. Habicht, Braun and Company (Box 187, Folder 2)
      - E.J. Wile and Company v. Rentner, Lustig Company (Box 187, Folder 3)
      - Fidelity Knitting Mills v. Mohawk Glove Corporation (Box 187, Folder 4)
      - The First National Corporation v. North American Copper Company, (2 Folders) (Box 187, Folder 5-6)
      - Francis A. Cundill and Company v. Federated Metals Corp. (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Hearn, John J. v. Pease and Elliman, Inc. (Folder 4)
      - Pacific Fur Corporation v. S. Rosenfelder and Son, Inc. (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Scheid, Theodore Mittelsten v. Compania Textilera Mexicana (Box 187, Folder 7)
      - Serota, David v. Leon A. Serota and Alexander M. Serota, (3 Folders) (Box 188, Folder 1-3)
      - S. Rosenfelder and Son, Inc. v. William Grossman (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Tappenbeck, William v. Caldbeck, Macgregor Exports, Ltd. (Box 188, Folder 4)
      - Thomas Moss and Sons, Ltd. v. Alfred L. Helwits and Company Inc. (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Tipton, Edna Sibley v. The Columbia Manicure Mfg. Company, Inc. (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - 1927
      - Charles Jacobs and Company v. W.R. Loxley and Company (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Glueck, Emil aka Alexander Glueck v. The Mojo-Schey Company, Inc. (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Hanish, Love and Company as agents for China Trading Corporation v. Borchmann and Stoffregen (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Hatzel and Buehler, Inc. v. L.A. Dreyfus Company, (2 Folders) (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
      - L.A. Dreyfus Company v. Thomas E. O’Brien (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Rothman, Philip v. Meyer Prince (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - S. Rosenfelder and Son, Inc. v. M.S. and J.A. Workman, Inc. (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Tappenbeck, William v. Schnabel, Gaumer and Company (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Thomas Moss and Sons, Ltd. v. Charles Kurlan (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Thomas Moss and Sons, Ltd. v. Charles Kurland, (3 Folders) (Box 42, Folder 2-4)
      - Wah Chang Trading Corporation v. Dodwell and Company, Ltd., (2 Folders) (Box 42, Folder 5-6)
    - 1928
      - Benjamin Griffen Glass Corp. v. Menger, Ring and Weinstein, Inc. (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Cuba Distilling Company v. Penick and Ford, Ltd. Inc. (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Cuba Distilling Company v. Penick and Ford Ltd., Inc., (2 Folders) (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
      - Cuba Distilling Company v. Penick and Ford, Ltd. Inc. (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Erwin Feldspar Company Inc. v. Richmond Mica Company (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Graves-Quinn Corp. v. Alfred C. Kihn, (3 Folders) (Box 149, Folder 1-3)
      - H.H. Butler Stores, Inc. v. Grinnell Lithographic Company Inc. (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - John Auerbach and Company v. Lamport Textile Company (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Ridley Watts and Company v. Bayer Brothers Corporation (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - 1929
      - Carrier Engineering Corporation v. Duplex Motion Picture Industries, (2 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 6-7)
      - The Duz Company, Inc. v. Armour and Company, (2 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
      - Graves-Quinn Corporation v. Alfred c. Kihn, (2 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
      - Graves-Quinn Corporation v. Alfred C. Kihn (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Punta Alegre Sugar Company v. Ralli Bros. (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Reiss, Massey and Co., Ltd. v. William J. Hauser (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Security Mills, Inc. v. Warwick Knitting Mills, Inc. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - 1930
      - Binger, Walter D. v. Cameron Clark (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Bingham and Co., Inc. v. William H. Waters, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Blythebourne Rainbow Laundry, Inc. v. James Beggs and Company, Inc., (2 Folders) (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
      - Burns Brothers v. Sir Lea Corp., Et Al., (2 Folders) (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
      - Cheetham and Co. v. Edward M. Poons Co. of Kobe, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Glen Eagle Corporation v. American Piece Dye Works, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Grover, Albert v. Morris A. Podvesoker (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Marinello Company v. National Display Card Company (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Newburger, Henderson and Loeb v. Samuel Goldberg (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Newburger, Henderson and Loeb v. William S. Jacobs (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Peterson, George H. v. S.P. Stein (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Robert H. Foederer, Inc. v. Societe Francaise Du Haut Yang Tze (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - S.S. Millinery Company, Inc. v. Bingham and Company as agents for Carlowitz and Company (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - W.W. Farrier Company v. Armour and Company (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - 1931
      - Bingham and Company, Inc. v. Arthur P. Morel (Box 188, Folder 6)
      - Castle, Benjamin F. v. Atlantic Exhibition Company Inc. (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Foley Brothers v. Port of New York Authority, (2 Folders) (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
      - Foley Brothers v. Port of New York Authority, (5 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 1-5)
      - Foley Brothers v. Port of New York Authority (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - The National Electric Heating Company, Inc. v. Acme Shellac Products Corporation (Box 188, Folder 7)
      - Sacks and Spiegelman v. Guide System and Supply Company (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Van Iderstine Company v. American Agricultural Chemical Company (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Van Iderstine Company v. American Agricultural Chemical Company, (3 Folders) (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
      - Van Perlstein and Roeper Bosch v. Favorite Panama Hat Co., Inc. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - 1932
      - Doherr, Grimm and Company, Inc. v. Felix Ries (Box 189, Folder 1)
      - Foley Brothers, Inc. v. The Port of New York Authority, (4 Folders) (Box 31, Folder 4-7)
      - Foley Brothers, Inc. v. The Port of New York Authority, (7 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 1-7)
      - Foley Brothers, Inc. v. The Port of New York Authority (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Ross, Minerva v. Newburger, Loeb and Company (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - 1933
      - Edmond Weil, Inc. v. Alfred Popper, (3 Folders) (Box 33, Folder 2-4)
      - Eubank, Gerald A. v. Hardcastle Pennock (Box 189, Folder 3)
      - J.H. Erstein and Bro. Inc. v. Frank and Dugan, Inc., (2 Folders) (Box 33, Folder 5-6)
    - 1934
      - A.S. Gold and Bro. Inc. v. Carlowitz-Bingham Fur Corp. (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Bingham and Company, Inc. as agents of Victorian Exports and Agencies Pty. Ltd. v. Nathan Berlin (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Chomsky, Nathan v. Morris Bushel (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Hartstein, Benjamin A. v. Samuel C. Lamport, (2 Folders) (Box 43, Folder 4-5)
      - James Beggs and Company Inc. v. Industrial Dyeing Corp. of America, (2 Folders) (Box 43, Folder 6-7)
      - M.S. and J.A. Workman, Inc. v. Carlowitz-Bingham Fur Corp. (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Reuter Brockelman and Company v. Mongolia Importing Company Inc. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - 1935
      - Silver, Abe J. v. Seligsberg and Company, (3 Folders) (Box 44, Folder 2-4)
      - Silver, Abe J. v. Seligsberg and Company, (3 Folders) (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
      - Silver, Abe J. v. Seligsberg and Company (Box 184, Folder 12)
    - 1936
      - G. Sack Inc. v. Olivier Produce Corp. (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Leibowitz, Jacob v. Weingarten and Company (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Meon, Howard C. v. Meon Engineering Corp., Meon Manufacturing Corp., Edward A. Joyce and William E. Steinback (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Perkins Hosiery Mills v. National Spinning Co., Inc., (2 Folders) (Box 149, Folder 4-5)
      - Stein, Hall and Co., Inc v. Bingham and Company (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Zinke, Louis P. v. Meon Manufacturing Company (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - 1937
      - Grantville Mills v. Beck Yarn Company (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - J. Nadler and Son, Inc. v. Bingham and Company, Inc. as Agents for Colyer, Watson and Company (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - S. Hirshenhorn and Sons v. Carl Wolter and Company (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - S. Hirshenhorn and Sons v. J. Gully and Company (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Turberg, Philip v. Orvis Bros. and Company, (2 Folders) (Box 45, Folder 5-6)
    - 1938
      - Cox, Samuel Houghton v. David B. Crockett, (2 Folders) (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
      - Jordan Mills, Inc. v. Pearl Yarn Company (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Luckmer, Dacie H. v. Weingarten and Company (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Murray Oil Products Co., Inc. v. Carlowitz and Co. (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Shapiro, Louis J. v. Auto-Lift Corporation of America (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Shapiro, Louis J. v. Auto-Lift Corporation of America, (4 Folders) (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
      - S. Hirshenhorn and Sons v. G. Colinet (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - 1939
      - Maliniac, Dr. Jacques W. v. Jackson Bros. Boesel and Company, (2 Folders) (Box 46, Folder 4-5)
      - Thomas, V.A. v. Skinner, Cook and Babcock, Inc. (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Wolf, Alfred M. v. Trans-Lux Corporation, (2 Folders) (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
    - 1940
      - Hanish, Love and Company v. Carl Wolter and Company (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - W.R. Grace and Company v. Southern Rice Sales Company Inc. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - 1941--Edmund Weil, Inc. v. Sociedade Industrial E. Mercantil (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 1942-- Silverman, Sol v. Louis Fruchter (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - 1943--A.A.Krejtman, Inc. v. Eugenio Lang, S.R.L. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 1946--International Technic, Inc. v. Harold D. Regar, (3 Folders) (Box 47, Folder 5-7)
    - 1948-- Poole, Sam and Nathan R. Kolansky v. T.O.D. Manufacturing Company, (2 Folders) (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
    - 1949
      - Carl M. Loeb Rhoades and Company v. Tecco Systems Company (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Orvis Brothers and Company v. Harry Copen, (2 Folders) (Box 48, Folder 4-5)
    - 1951
      - Burney, Mark v. Jacob Louis and Dorota Louis (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Orvis Brothers and Company v. Morton P. Allen and Agnes H. Allen (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - 1961--H. Hentz and Company v. Rene D. Lyon (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - 1962--Orvis Brothers and Company v. Irwin Keller (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - 1966
      - Cyprus Mines Corporation v. Compania Espanola de Minas de Rio Tinto (Box 189, Folder 6)
      - Jordan Mills Inc. v. Textile Jobbers Company (Box 189, Folder 7)
      - Jordan Mills Inc. v. Textile Jobbers Company (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - 1969
      - Orvis Brothers and Company v. Bobby McGuire (Box 190, Folder 2)
      - Orvis Brothers and Company v. Donald F. Kern (Box 190, Folder 3)
      - Orvis Brothers and Company v. Quentin Still (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - 1970--Orvis Brothers and Company v. Victor J. Miller (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - 1971--Orvis Brothers and Company v. James J. White (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - 1972--Winslow, Cohu and Stetson, Inc. v. Charles M. Greenspan (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - 1973--Hayden, Stone Inc. v. William L. Canfield (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - Subseries V.2: Case Correspondence, 1914-1930